[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":36079,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":46034,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":25053,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":71087,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":13879,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":84967,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":6726,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":91694,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2819,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":94514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":780,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":95295,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6  to get  your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4976,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":100271,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1055,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":101326,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":1602,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":102929,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub> 6</sub>  1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":829,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":103758,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1589,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":105347,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":550,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":105897,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you star t with t he first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7426,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":113323,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":638,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":113961,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1290,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":115252,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":639,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":115891,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":29791,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":145682,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":729,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":146412,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":149403,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":719,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":150122,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or big ger, you  subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4095,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":154217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":705,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":154923,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":21957,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":176881,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":8202,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":185083,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":26587,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":211670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":864,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":212535,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":1472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":214007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":515,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":214523,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is t he inver se of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1759,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":216282,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":678,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":216960,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1317,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":218277,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":434,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":218711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2948,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":221659,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2962,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":224621,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":2531,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":227153,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br / ><br />  However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":22135,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":249289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":5964,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":255254,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":7223,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":262477,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3589,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":266066,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1850,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":267916,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator unde r +<sub> 6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":1982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":269899,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":662,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":270562,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":5314,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":275877,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":732,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":276609,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining ques tions as  accurately as possible.","rt":8121,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":284731,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4210,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":288941,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":632,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":289574,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":1653,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":291229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2812,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":294041,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":1462,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":295504,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":2136,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":297640,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2707,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":300347,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5,four plus one is five and it's not above nine so it's fine","response_history":["5,four plus one is five and it's not above 9","5,four plus one is five and it's not above nine so it's fine"],"rt":19205,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":319552,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3,eight plus four is twelve but it's above nine so you subtract nine from it","response_history":["3,eight plus four is twelve but it's above nine so you subtract nine from it"],"rt":20274,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":339827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 because you can combine it with other numbers and it just copies them","response_history":["0 because it's the opposite ","0 because it'","0 because it","0 because i","0 because ","0 because you can combine it with other numbers and it just copies them"],"rt":44091,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":383919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":16265,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":400185,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":1708,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":401894,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":1519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":403413,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 because three is six under nine","response_history":["6 because three is six under nine"],"rt":13752,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":417165,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because you can't make every other number with it","response_history":["no because you can't make every other number with it"],"rt":12768,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":429935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes because you can make every other number with it","response_history":["yes because you can make every other number with it"],"rt":7726,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":437661,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because you can't make every other number with i t","response_history":["no because you can't make every other number with it"],"rt":8759,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":446421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because you can't make every other number with it","response_history":["yes be","yes b","yes ","no because you can't make every other number with it"],"rt":10615,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":457036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary  value if  necessary.","rt":9453,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":466490,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"8","response_history":["8"],"rt":18054,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":484545,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"9-x because the inverse is what you combine it with to make nine","response_history":["x-","x","9-x because the inverse is what you combine it with to make nine"],"rt":32446,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":516992,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a  pattern  to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no there's no pattern you have to check whether it makes them all","response_history":["t","no there's no pattern you have to check whether it makes them all"],"rt":20023,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":537015,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4359,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":541375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":3036,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":544411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["False","True"],"rt":9973,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":554384,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"true because x is always related to n","response_history":["true bec ause x i s always related to n"],"rt":31336,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":585720,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":7460,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":593181,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"sometimes because it sometimes is and sometimes isn't with no pattern","response_history":["sometimes because it sometim es is an d someth","sometimes because it sometimes is and sometimes isn't with no pattern"],"rt":31029,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":624210,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":4958,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":629168,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1241,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":630410,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"25","response_history":["25"],"rt":1925,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":632336,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":2194,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":634531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"algebra","response_history":["algebra"],"rt":11237,"trial_type":"quest ion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":645768,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["3 - seen it used or explained","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":7519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":653287,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, re member a nd understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","response_history":["3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":4317,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":657604,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2258,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":659863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2566,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":662430,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2063,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":664493,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1834,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":666328,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","response_history":["eb","english"],"rt":4721,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":671049,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":3260,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":674309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":2559,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":676869,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]